Contact

rn3082@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-lamaire-rn-bsn-ccrn-759371132 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Cardiac Care Basic Life Support (BLS)

Certifications

BLS CCRN

Jennifer LaMaire RN, BSN, CCRN

Clinical Nurse Liaison at Gulfside Hospice & Pasco Palliative Care Dade City

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Hospice & Palliative Medicine, Intensive Care, Cardiac Care, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional as a Certified Critical Care Registered Nurse and holding a Bachelor's Degree focused in Nursing Science from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

Gulfside Hospice & Pasco Palliative Care Clinical Nurse Liaison April 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months) Dade City, Florida

AdventHealth
Critical Care Nurse
December 2018 - March 2019 (4 months)

Tampa General Hospital
Critical Care Registered Nurse, BSN, CCRN
October 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 3 months)
Tampa, Florida

MSICU

Suncoast Hospice | Empath Health Registered Nurse, BSN, CCRN February 2017 - October 2017 (9 months) Clearwater, Florida

Specializing in Hospice and Palliative care treatment provided within the home setting.

Largo Medical Center Critical Care Nurse January 2012 - February 2017 (5 years 2 months) Largo, Florida

Registered Nurse within the critical care setting. Provided direct patient care in a busy intensive care unit that focuses on cardiac thoracic interventions and numerous surgical procedures.

Education

Grand Canyon University
Bachelor's Degree, Nursing Science · (2014 - 2016)

Galen College of Nursing
Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2011)

Pinellas Technical Education Center-Clearwater LPN, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training · (2006 - 2007)